Hello friends, my name is Sachin and
yes, today you saw it right that Max
Bupa is the main product of this name Nibha. Now the
name of this company has changed. The
name of the company has become Nibha. So friends, let me
tell you why this happened.
Friends, on 23rd September 2021, Max Bupa
sent this mail to all their partners and all their customers who have taken policies from Max Bupa
that our shareholding subsequent to our
shareholding change, more than 120
holdings had changed. Maxis no longer a
shareholder here, that is, the company which was Max
India, which you know, in the
name of Max Hospital, in the name of Max Health Care,
it was their partner, it had
exited from here in 2019. Thanks, we do not have the
procedure of using the user name, which means we
cannot use their name.
They have decided that since December 2004, they will
not use the admin name. Till now, the
name which was being used for that was Max
Bupa.  It was on royalty in Mexico
but the background
was their shareholding, that had already changed here,
you will see that when they are
rebranding their brand, they are
saying that our new brand is giving, that is, giving a
giving look to
everyone and our name Nibha is derived from a Sanskrit word that means Nibha means Sanskrit,
whose name Nibha
means Sandhi in Sanskrit, that is,
Sun means
man, so let me tell you a little
about the background of this company,
which will make things more clear to you and
friends, earlier the holding of Maximum Per was
1% after Max India, that is,
50% of Max India's share was held by Max Bupa Chandan
and Fufa's 59% was
held by Max India, here Max India had
more shareholding,
but in February 2019,
Max exited from it and whatever
holding of that has to be bought, it has to be bought, it is a North Do
Not Care System Function Company, Settle
Total  They have
bought 55.58% of their holding, so the
holding that Bupa is left with is now
44.42%, which means the
main stakeholder here is True North, that is why the
company here is now
changing its name, rebranding.
You must have seen some time ago that what used to be Rally
Health Insurance had
changed its name to Vijay and entered Care Help,
but friends, the most common
question people have is
what difference will it make to our body, so
friends, let me tell you that the company was
earlier workers, their management was earlier, the
management is almost the same, there will be
no changes in the plane, the facilities that were being given to you earlier,
SIM, the same
facilities will still be given, the way your
network was earlier, the hospital network is
also going to remain the same, so friends, here the
only shareholder is Transports, the
shareholding pattern has changed,
apart from that nothing has happened here and the
company has changed its name from Max Bupa to
Nimbu, so friends, I hope
you  You must have liked this information,
if you liked it then share it, but yes
still if you have any question related to your policy like
what will happen to our policy and how will it work then
you
can ask me by WhatsApping my number, I will
definitely answer your questions, my name is
Sachin Verma,
Ajay, thank you very much for watching this video.